What does race have to do with environmental injustice?
The land that they are seizing is indigenous land.
We are right now on stolen land.
The government is seizing indigenous land to toss additional garbage.
I don't want to be sounding like doom and gloom, but I'm just trying to explain the situation.
And often you'll hear folks like me, we're alarmed.
There's a panic in our voice.
You know, we're very passionate because what's happening is extremely violating.
It's violating to the earth and it's violating to each other as humans.
And the folks that are the most affected are frontline communities.
And often they are either people in the global south or people here in the United States that
are purposefully discarded and discredited communities, purposefully and systemically
erased communities, oppressed communities, you know, and it's not just by chance.
It's designed this way.